One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I guess... I must have hit my head when we fell.
Me too, my head hurts quite a bit.
I can't believe we lost him.
I wonder if the samurai's still okay.
Says the guy who took us on a massive detour.
All of us just followed the path, didn't we?!
Sadly we never managed to find
the abominable snowman, even after searching.
But I'll never forget those shadows I saw.
It wasn't the abominable snowman. Don't get carried away.
You said the whole thing
was just an ambush, didn't you?
I did not!
Well, I'm still not a believer.
I believe they exist!
I believe that I need more evidence before I decide.
Wow, that's a very good position to take.
You really are mature.
Well, I have been alive and dead for many years.
Indecision is a sign of weakness.
What?
Hey! Samurai-san! Where are you?
Don't you dare hurt Nami's beautiful body!
Hey, both of you! Please come look at this!
Footprints!
Th-This is...
You don't suppose these could be
the footprints of the legendary abominable snowman?!
Hey now, how can you say something so stupid?
Wow, really?!
Mysterious footprints on a snow covered mountain?!
They're huge, aren't they?! I can't believe it!
And they're fresh!
If we follow them, then...
We'll solve a mystery of the unknown!
A dead end?
What are they? There are giant shadows behind us!
Could it be the abominable-
What's this gas?!
It'sh like I'm drunk or somethin...
Shuddenly my tung feelsh all heavy... An' I'm sleeby...
C-C-Could dis be an ambuth?
No matter how good your alcohol tolerance is, if you breath in KYP gas...
you will experience a drunken state
and overwhelming drowsiness.
And at the bottom of the cliff is zone F-16.
You will not be able to escape the ice spikes!
So these three will fall first.
Spikes?!
Hey, guys!
T-That was close.
This is zone F-16. We found the three Straw Hat
pirates exactly where they were reported to be.
We'll dispose of the corpses now.
Who're you calling a corpse?
What?! She's alive!
But it's only one woman against all of us-
I don't care how many
of you third-rate weaklings there are.
It's all the same to me!
I gotta be careful.
After all, this is the body of the delicate Nami-san.
It'd be a crime to leave any scars on it.
Forgive me, Nami-san. Just one cig.
Now then...
Get up, you idiots!
Anyway, the time
for mysteries of the unknown is over.
So, is this the area the samurai went?
Yes.
I presume he's searching for his torso somewhere around the lake.
Well, we're almost to the lake.
Samurai-san!
Hey! Samurai!
Get out here, Samurai!
Samurai!
Were you killed in battle?
Get out here! You okay?
Samurai!
Do you hear me, Samurai-san?!
I really wonder where he went.
Do you think he got his torso
and went off to find that kid of his?
Huh?
Isn't this the samurai?!
What the... he's frozen!
Hey, hey!
Cold!
Hey, are you okay?
Did somebody attack you?
For some unknown reason,
I was frozen and on the verge of meeting my demise!
You mean you were freezing to death in the blizzard?!
No! I-I-I-It is not even remotely cold!
Damn you're stubborn!
A warrior does not feel cold!
Man, this guy's a pain.
Put some clothes on!
Isn't your power the ability to create clothes?!
A-Actually, because of that magic, I have a weak point.
I-I can't claim to be a strong swimmer...
You sink! Everyone knows that!
S-So it seems that my torso...
has f-fallen in water.
In water?
I-I'm certain!
I can feel that my torso's underwater...
I see. So that's why you were laying here freezing.
If your body's in the water,
then you can't use your ability.
If it's in water, then do you think
that maybe it fell in that lake, Brook?
I would think so.
I heard that the lake's technically part of the ocean.
If he's still alive,
then that means the sharks haven't gotten it yet.
But we have no idea what else is in that lake.
We'd better pull it out as fast as possible.
Yes, let's hurry.
I-If it's in the lake... then I'll have to dive for it...
We get it! You swim like a hammer, right?
Bungling samurai.
You're pirates, aren't you?!
Why would you go so far
to help someone you've never met before?
I told you,
I know the difference between right and wrong!
And I wanna settle our fight
after I put you back together!
I'm gonna give you a beating.
F-Forgive me.
I'm indebted to you.
Oh, so I see you learned how to express gratitude.
I guess some people
improve with a little freezing now and again.
What's that?
I was wondering myself.
Th-That's...
Brownbeard-san's underling-taurs,
whom we stripped of clothes!
Pull yourself together! You gotta run!
Get away from the lake!
There's a monster on the other side!
We have to report it to Master!
Where could something like that have been hiding on this island?!
Just run! The monster's coming!
Huh? A monster? Aren't you guys all monsters?
It's those damned thieving pirates from before!
Dammit, that's my coat!
Leave the coat! Run! Just get back to the laboratory!
Those guys took out the boss!
We won't forget!
What was that about?
I have no idea.
Hey, Brook. They were coming
from the direction of the lake, weren't they?
Whoa! That's right! You actually got that right!
That's amazing, Zoro-san!
But why are you looking like that?
Well, I don't quite remember...
there being a mountain there.
Hmm... a mountain?
W-What is that thing?!
Smiley is the explosion that destroyed Punk Hazard
four years ago, a living chemical weapon!
Did they really believe
that I would just destroy all the gas on the island?
No!
Who would waste such a precious thing?
I compressed it and turned it into a monster!
A monster named Smiley!
This island was an unlivable hellscape due to what enveloped it!
People can forget such tragedies all too quickly,
but it hasn't gone anywhere!
It's still right here in the palm of my hand!
They've captured the ship!
Stop the ship!
Quit playing around! Hurry and wrap it up!
S-Smoker-san! How do I change back to normal?
You're in the way! Just sit there and be quiet!
Don't you have the door open yet?!
Our enemy is inside the lab.
We can't just waste time out here until we die!
It's no use! The door won't budge an inch, Smo-san!
What a load of crap.
If only I had my body,
breaking into this place wouldn't be a problem.
Your power sure is useful!
Did we just teleport?
Get into the bag and stay quiet.
We're already at the back entrance of the lab.
The main experiment room
will have Caesaro and a woman in it.
I'll get them out of there one way or another.
When that happens, you investigate the drugs.
But you're so strong
and can easily get close to Master.
Why don't you just capture him yourself?
Then I could have all the time in the world
to investigate the drugs.
I have my reasons for not doing that. It's why I need your strength.
Anyway,
the faster you guys can kidnap Caesaro the better.
Then I'll take care of the rest.
Hey! Look at that!
Something's flying toward us!
It's a giant bomb!
No, it's something else!
Bam!
"Bam!"? Was that a person?
Damn!
That was a pretty good shortcut!
Master! Get out here!
I'm gonna kick your ass and kidnap you!
Luffy, you're supposed to keep that a secret.
Straw Hat?!
It's the Straw Hat Pirates!
Go, Luffy!
That idiot.
Who told him to take on the entire Navy?
Where are you Master?! Get out here!
It's amazing! I can hardly believe my eyes.
Oh, wait... I don't have any eyes.
Caesar's Laboratory - Main Entrance
Did that bastard just say that he's going to
kick our beloved Master's ass and kidnap him?!
What a joke! Kill the Straw Hat Pirates!
We got here alright, but where's Master?
I doubt he'd hang around outside.
Then where is he?
Probably inside the lab.
I see.
Then I guess we have to get through that giant door.
Let's go.
Straw Hat Luffy!
What are you plotting on this island?
Smoke-man! I'm so glad you're alright!
It looked like you took a beating earlier,
so I was worried.
Don't mock me.
Huh? Does your stomach hurt? Are you constipated?
It flew!
What's with you, Smoke-man? You've gotten weak.
N-No, that's not it. I'm...
And besides,
the way you've been talking has been weird, too.
Hey, give me a damn break!
Don't lose to him in my body!
Huh, that weapon!
So you're back on the seas, huh, Straw Hat?
But I won't let you do as you please!
I got hit!
That's right... There's Sea Stone in that thing!
When did Four-eyes get this strong?
What was her name again?
I'm Smoker!
Luffy, this is certainly Law's doing.
Oh, they've swapped bodies. I see.
No wonder he's so weak.
So that means...
you're...
Smoke-man?!
What're you laughing at?!
Fight me, Straw Hat!
I can't catch him!
Our fight will have to wait 'til next time!
What're you saying?
There's no point in fighting
if you aren't at full strength!
Cocky bastard!
See ya later, Smoke-man!
They blew a hole in the door!
Who is that guy?
Was that a laser?!
Luffy, Robin! I busted the door open! Let's go in!
Wow, you work fast, Franky!
Smokey!
Something strange is flying toward us!
Over there!
What is that?
What...
is that?
Luffy, Franky, wait!
Wh-What is that?
It's poison gas! Get back!
If you cut or shoot it, then poison gas comes out.
Get your gas masks on! Hurry!
Eh? What's that?
Is it alive?
What could it possibly be? I have no idea.
Hey! What the hell is that?
I don't know. I've never seen anything like it.
It fell from the sky, right?
Yeah, but it's moving.
Man, how creepy.
Is that thing alive?
Look at that!
They're merging and growing bigger.
We should just push it into the river.
Hey! Don't do that!
More poison gas!
Pull him out!
Heave, ho!
Oh man...
My skin! It hurts! Do something! Anybody!
Hey, get a cloth or something!
I knew you shouldn't touch it!
What do we do?
I don't know!
You guys can fall back!
This thing looks like it'd be weak against fire.
Let's burn it down!
Yeah!
Take this!
There ain't a creature alive that isn't afraid of fire!
Damn, you're smart.
Kill it with fire!
I knew fire would work. Serves you right!
It's starting to burn! It doesn't like it at all!
My men!
What was that?
No clue. First time I've ever seen anything like it.
It's poisonous to touch, and it blows up if you burn it.
I couldn't even tell if it was alive or not!
Well, whatever it was... it's dead now.
Yeah, you're right.
And what's more,
the explosion took out the marines stealing the ship.
It worked out pretty good for us!
It's back!
Look at the sky!
Those are all the same as the first one?
There's so many of them.
They're falling like rain!
Run away! And don't touch them!
Smoker-san. It's too dangerous to stay here.
We need to find shelter.
What a good boy!
I'm sorry I had you locked up for three years.
Master!
Why are you out here? It's too dangerous!
I knew it.
There's no doubt about it. You're Caesar Clown!
Are you that Master guy?
Indeed I am.
Get a good look at me,
Straw Hat Pirate Crew and Navy G-5 division.
I am the number one scientist in the world!
Master Caesar Clown!
It won't be long now.
He doesn't like the water...
so he's launching little pieces of himself over here
so that he can get across the lake.
From the Burning Lands to the Frozen Lands!
Once every single piece has made it over here...
you will get the full taste of...
the living chemical weapon that is the explosion that laid waste to Punk Hazard four years ago.
It turned this island into a landscape of death
where nothing could survive!
Is that thing alive?
I have no idea. I've never seen anything like it.
A mysterious thing...
...doing mysterious things.
Gotcha!